Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
The Wizard King of the World
Stupid. No, it's wrong. I mean me, of all people. How could they even consider kicking me out? You know? I have more magic power than any royalty and they just toss me aside like garbage.
Doesn't make sense. Magic is supposed to be everything. Right?
Mock me! How dare they!
Do you have an audience for your incessant rambling?
Huh? Just talking to myself. Everything is in place now.
Alright. Just wait, Knights of the Clover Kingdom. You'll soon see my power in all its glory!
Glory!
Outplay
Forget about it!
Let's depart from the moon
良いのとり生まれたいさ obligate every time
このころのどこかで涙の夜を壊してよ
いつか射す光へ約束を守りたいんだ
my God
you
you don't need to front away from people like this Noelle
I
Commoner. Rat. Disgrace. Failure. Do you think I care if I fit in with you people? Watch, because I will!
That's enough out of you, little rat. We will not be spoken to in such a manner by your kind. Be quiet.
Not a chance! How dare you!
You better listen up, because I wasn't done talking! I'm going to get results like no one has before!
I'll do whatever it takes to become the Wizard King and prove you wrong!
A-ah!
Oster…
Not a chance.
You become the Wizard King?
A mere commoner.
You've got to be joking!
Water-binding magic, now cease up its coils!
Impossible.
Mist-binding magic, Mist-Spider's Thread spell.
So it's true, he's nullifying our magic.
This kid is no ordinary commoner.
We'll take him.
With an attack range like that, we have nothing to fear.
Sand creation magic. Sand armored guard.
He's in trouble.
Is this necessary? I'm sure he's learned his lesson.
Did I ask you to speak?
No, sir.
Such behavior cannot go unpunished.
Especially when it interferes with a grand occasion like the Distinguished Service Ceremony banquet.
Now, now. Why so gentle?
Don't tell me the Golden Dawn's getting soft, Alec Dora.
Restraining him's not enough.
Presumptuous fellows like this need their lessons beaten into them.
Don't do it!
This will shut that mouth of yours for good.
Please, Zalad, no!
Holy Water Bullet!
Asta!
Could there be any greater disgrace than you?
I'm not done yet!
Now apologize!
I've been brought to my knees, bested by a commoner.
You pay for striking back at me!
This time I won't show any mercy!
Please stop, Solid! You don't need to do this!
You don't need to do this!
I don't need to do this!
Nozel!
Nozel! What are you doing?!
Nozel, what are you doing?
Enough, Solid.
You shouldn't be so quick to use your magic against a mere commoner.
He deserved it, though!
I said enough.
Do you wish to sully the name of House Silva with your antics?
The air, it's freezing.
This ice-cold pressure, it's different from Captain Yami's.
So this is the captain of the Silver Eagles.
A commoner who dares to defy royalty.
I wonder how I should punish you.
Now he's involved too?
This is spinning out of control.
This is gone far enough.
What are you thinking, ganging up on a lone youth like this?
Where is your sense of honor?
It turns out that Mimosa was right.
Oh yeah, you are one entertaining kid.
Huh?
And today is your lucky day, because I, Leopold Vermillion, have just made you my rival.
Now what was your name again?
Costa or something?
No, Leopold, I told you, remember?
It's Asta!
Asta, that's right.
And a fine name it is, rival of mine.
I'm a little confused here.
Come on, what are you waiting for?
This is cause for celebration!
Now celebrate.
Um, woohoo?
you're related yes that's right Fuegolion and Leopold are my cousins on my father's side
Fuegolion and Leopold are brothers my father's elder brother is their father
oh and you know Noelle is my cousin too her mother was my mother's elder sister
that's kind of a lot to take in hey uh I appreciate the offer but I already have a rival
you know over there so it's not like there's a rule somewhere that says you can only have one
rival wait are you being serious oh your robe covers them up but those are some big muscles
you got there I expect no less from a rival of mine now let's arm wrestle why it's really amazing
how dumb guys can be sometimes I'm sure where are your manners hush okay sorry sir you will address
me as captain soul oh right sorry about that jar don't worry it won't happen again
okay sir well come on you want to do this right now just a friendly arm wrestling deathmatch between
rivals strong enough and brave enough to be Leopold's rifle this is an awful lot of excitement for a
banquet oh at least things appear to have calmed down a royal has recognized a commoner as his rival
truly
hmm remember Nozel the wizard king himself invited this young man to attend the ceremony
he is a commoner but we can still extend him a measure of acceptance
I would never have expected to hear such nonsense being spouted by a royal
I'm sorry to see how soft house vermilion has grown you're a disgrace to the family
Fuegolion what did you say as an eagle soaring the skies how can I ever accept an insect who crawls
upon the ground
two captains pitting mana against mana what a battle wow amazing can you feel it I may not be able to
detect mana but I can tell these guys are something else we should probably stop them
huh sir no soul let the boys play out their little rivalry and call me captain
right shower whatever you say that's captain
uh terrible news what is it sir the royal capital it's under attack
uh
such revolting creatures i wonder where they came from invading the royal capital what were they
thinking what are these things they've been shot clean through but they keep coming stand firm
it's our duty to protect the club you feel right you're not protecting anything today
you're nothing but scum scum scum my god what kind of power is this
you're so sure you're stronger than me right right then come on and show yourself magic knights
what do you mean the royal capital is under attack
i'll use my stone creation magic stone model of the world will show us
that looks like a model of the noble realm wow so cool
it's even reproduced people's voices in magic
he must send mana through a given area creating a replica here simultaneously
this spell's detail and artistry far outstrip my magic flower guidepost
for troops with this much power to strike five places at once without us noticing
yes a skilled spatial magic user must have transported them all inside simultaneously
except how could that happen the noble realm's guardian mages maintain a constant magic barrier
around it which should render it impervious to invasion by spatial magic
were they able to find some way to break through the barrier
or worse did a guardian mage turn traitor
in any case this took extraordinary skill
we need to decide how best to allocate our resources
the castle area takes priority
what's everyone waiting for
people are getting killed and standing around talking's not gonna help them
i'm out of here
osta wait just where do you think you're going we still don't have a grip on the situation
and besides what will you do when you can't even detect magic power
i'm just gonna go wherever it's loudest
what are you some kind of animal
now we're talking wait up osta i'm not gonna miss seeing my rival in action
it's really amazing how silly guys can be sometimes i'm sure
yes it is and call me captain
really leo must you be such a child
i can see i'm going to have to take you in hand
it may chafe taking orders from me
still we must act now
i'll go after leo and the black bull boy
and then once i've secured them we'll head to the north
black bull girl you're with me
silver eagles take the central district where the enemy is strongest
very well
blue rose knights you head east
as loath as i am to take a man's orders we must
i'm ready whenever you are shar
call me captain soul
golden dawn split into two teams
one heads northwest the other west
we will safeguard the people of the noble realm
let's hurry
i hate to leave before dessert but i suppose we can come back for it later
failure today will bring shame to the magic knights do not let the enemy get
away
right
i hope it's the riot ocean again for the frangie food but now it looks like something serious is going down
it's time to get out there and make a grand charmy entrance
who knows if i do really well maybe i'll get some even fancier food as a reward
what is this delicious smell
can't very well go fight on an empty zeppuccino
you won't get away with this
what do you want whatever it is you can have it
there are civilians careful
oh yeah sorry about that char call me captain
this cowardly invasion ends now you will scatter before our magic
whatever these creatures are half-hearted
attacks will have little effect on them in which case
oh
ha ha ha ha
dessert's waiting let's work up an appetite shall we
don't think you'll get away with this we will annihilate you
what are they some strange army i've never seen anything like them where's asta
tell me little girl do you like it here in the clover kingdom
yes i do i love it so please sir
please you need to stop
i can't i hate the clover kingdom
so i'm going to take this town its people
and you little girl
and destroy you all
all right then i'm going to protect them
and
you
Oh oh oh...
乾いた感情があの日の僕を見つめ
突き動かしてる
I can trust yourיא
消えそうな光でも闇を照らす力が
I'm going to change the time and the flow of the flow.
I'm believing in you.
I'm not believing in you.
Break free yourself.
If you're not a dream,
I'll take you to the next step.
Do you wanna drive?
僕の命が終わるまで
どんな痛みも受け入れよう
We can drive down, we can drive down
たとえ明日が見えなくても
声にならない
想いを抱いて
叫び続ける in my heart
I'm just gonna go wherever it's loudest!
What are you, some kind of animal?
An animal?
What? What?
Oh, yes!
A dog!
That would be adorable!
Although a sweet kitty cat would be nice, too!
Meow, meow!
That might be even better!
Wait, maybe...
Something a little more wild and fierce,
like a wolf!
All men are wolves sometimes, baby!
No, it's impossible!
They simply can't choose!
None of the above!
These creatures are disgusting!
But there's no time to waste being squeamish now!
We must keep the Clover Kingdom's people safe!
Black Clover, page 22, wild magic dance!
Anybody who's been injured, please come see me!